[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_22",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_01_searchwalsham_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_02_meetgalahad_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p5",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p5",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_alt_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_03_lostvillages_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_04_corruptedresources_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc1",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 31,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_05_findingfort_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_05",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_06_lostcathedral_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Sun_p2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_06",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_07_cursedcemetery_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_07",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_08_azothtree_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p6",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_08",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_09_killumberto_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 34,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p9",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 34,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Yonas_p9",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 2,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_09",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_alt_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQ2_2hFishingPole_Yonas",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_10_cleansefort_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "Brightwoodv2Arc2",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 34,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "99B_Galahad_p8",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_10",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_objective_title",
        "Description": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99B_MSQ_11_weaversvector_complete_available_response",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
